Guide to the Chet Huntley Papers 1912-2017
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Photographs, circa 1920-1974; Series IX; 2.0 linear feet and one oversize box
  - Huntley early broadcast, undated; 78(IX):193 (Box-folder 16/93)
  - Huntley in an early NBC interview, undated; 78(IX):194 (Box-folder 16/94)
  - joking with co-workers, undated; 78(IX):195 (Box-folder 16/95)
  - candid shot of Huntley, undated; 78(IX):196 (Box-folder 16/96)
  - CBS Huntley with two un-identified men, undated; 78(IX):197 (Box-folder 16/97)
  - broadcasting during an early war, undated; 78(IX):198 (Box-folder 16/98)
  - "weather reports from the stratosphere: Huntley, Dr. Irving Krick, Associate Yuan, Dr. Carl Anderson", undated; 78(IX):199 (Box-folder 16/99)
  - accepting award, undated; 78(IX):200 (Box-folder 16/100)
  - "Randolph Scott, Walter Brennen", undated; 78(IX):201 (Box-folder 17/01)
  - 1938 broadcast, 78(IX):202 (Box-folder 17/02)
  - "staff softball game 1940", 78(IX):203 (Box-folder 17/03)
  - "P-61 Nightfighter aerial shot", undated; 78(IX):204 (Box-folder 17/04)
  - Huntley Brinkley reporting, undated; 78(IX):205 (Box-folder 17/05)
  - Huntley with 5 un-identified men, undated; 78(IX):206 (Box-folder 17/06)
  - March of Dimes, undated; 78(IX):207 (Box-folder 17/07)
  - reporting from a Navy vessel, undated; 78(IX):208 (Box-folder 17/08)
  - interview from a Navy ship, undated; 78(IX):209 (Box-folder 17/09)
  - KNX photo, undated; 78(IX):210 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - "Thomas Lee Army Air Force pilot B-25", undated; 78(IX):211 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - P-61, undated; 78(IX):212 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):213 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - broadcasting, undated; 78(IX):214 (Box-folder 17/14)
  - crash test simulator, undated; 78(IX):215 (Box-folder 17/15)
  - Huntley with two government officials, undated; 78(IX):216 (Box-folder 17/16)
  - interview with un-identified man, undated; 78(IX):217 (Box-folder 17/17)
  - construction of dam, undated; 78(IX):218 (Box-folder 17/18)
  - KNX photo interview, undated; 78(IX):219 (Box-folder 17/19)
  - broadcasting with two other men, undated; 78(IX):220 (Box-folder 17/20)
  - "George Armistead and Chet Huntley February 6, 1945", 78(IX):221 (Box-folder 17/21)
  - dam construction, undated; 78(IX):222 (Box-folder 17/22)
  - CBS military broadcast, undated; 78(IX):223 (Box-folder 17/23)
  - portrait David Brinkley, undated; 78(IX):224 (Box-folder 17/24)
  - "last night at NBC 1970", 78(IX):225 (Box-folder 17/25)
  - "last night at NBC 1970", 78(IX):226 (Box-folder 17/26)
  - "last night at NBC 1970", 78(IX):227 (Box-folder 17/27)
  - "last night at NBC 1970", 78(IX):228 (Box-folder 17/28)
  - UVALDE chamber of commerce award, undated; 78(IX):229 (Box-folder 17/29)
  - Melvin Rowland and Chet Huntley UVALDE Honorary Mayor Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):230 (Box-folder 17/30)
  - Huntley accepting award, undated; 78(IX):231 (Box-folder 17/31)
  - Huntley in group photo, undated; 78(IX):232 (Box-folder 17/32)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." I, 78(IX):233 (Box-folder 17/33)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." II, 78(IX):234 (Box-folder 17/34)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." III, 78(IX):235 (Box-folder 17/35)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." IV, 78(IX):236 (Box-folder 17/36)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." V, 78(IX):237 (Box-folder 17/37)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." VI, 78(IX):238 (Box-folder 17/38)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." VII, 78(IX):239 (Box-folder 17/39)
  - "Huntley-Reagan 1968 Republican Convention L.A." VIII, 78(IX):240 (Box-folder 17/40)
  - Huntley-Brinkley JFK Oval Office I, undated; 78(IX):241 (Box-folder 17/41)
  - Huntley-Brinkley JFK Oval Office II, undated; 78(IX):242 (Box-folder 17/42)
  - Huntley-Brinkley JFK Oval Office III, undated; 78(IX):243 (Box-folder 17/43)
  - Huntley-Brinkley JFK Oval Office V, undated; 78(IX):244 (Box-folder 17/44)
  - arriving from airplane, 1969; 78(IX):245 (Box-folder 17/45)
  - greetings arriving in Dayton, 1969; 78(IX):246 (Box-folder 17/46)
  - greetings arriving in Dayton, 1969; 78(IX):247 (Box-folder 17/47)
  - meeting, 1969; 78(IX):248 (Box-folder 17/48)
  - meeting "Don Dahlman", 1969; 78(IX):249 (Box-folder 17/49)
  - "The Phil Donahue Show" I, 1969; 78(IX):250 (Box-folder 17/50)
  - "The Phil Donahue Show" II, 1969; 78(IX):252 (Box-folder 17/51)
  - "The Phil Donahue Show" III, 1969; 78(IX):253 (Box-folder 17/52)
  - "The Phil Donahue Show" IV, 1969; 78(IX):254 (Box-folder 17/53)
  - "The Phil Donahue Show" V, 1969; 78(IX):255 (Box-folder 17/54)
  - "luncheon at the Statler" I, 1969; 78(IX):256 (Box-folder 17/55)
  - "luncheon at the Statler" I, 1969; 78(IX):257 (Box-folder 17/56)
  - "luncheon at the Statler" III, 1969; 78(IX):258 (Box-folder 17/57)
  - "luncheon at the Statler" IV, 1969; 78(IX):259 (Box-folder 17/58)
  - "luncheon at the Statler" V Mayor Hall, 1969; 78(IX):260 (Box-folder 17/59)
  - "The News" I Huntley/Phil Donahue/Ed Hamlyn, 1969; 78(IX):261 (Box-folder 17/60)
  - "The News" II Ed Hamlyn, 1969; 78(IX):262 (Box-folder 17/61)
  - "The News" III, 1969; 78(IX):263 (Box-folder 17/62)
  - "The News" IV, 1969; 78(IX):264 (Box-folder 17/63)
  - "The News" V, 1969; 78(IX):265 (Box-folder 17/64)
  - "NCR Auditorium" I, 1969; 78(IX):266 (Box-folder 17/65)
  - "NCR Auditorium" II, 1969; 78(IX):267 (Box-folder 17/66)
  - "NCR Auditorium" III, 1969; 78(IX):268 (Box-folder 17/67)
  - "NCR Auditorium" IV, 1969; 78(IX):269 (Box-folder 17/68)
  - "NCR Auditorium" V, 1969; 78(IX):270 (Box-folder 17/69)
  - "A Day In Dayton" I, 1969; 78(IX):271 (Box-folder 17/70)
  - "A Day In Dayton" II with Phil Donahue, 1969; 78(IX):272 (Box-folder 17/71)
  - "A Day In Dayton" III with Phil Donahue, 1969; 78(IX):273 (Box-folder 17/72)
  - "A Day In Dayton" IV, 1969; 78(IX):274 (Box-folder 17/73)
  - "A Day In Dayton" V, 1969; 78(IX):275 (Box-folder 17/74)
  - portrait of a newscaster, undated; 78(IX):276 (Box-folder 17/75)
  - NBC Photo 1967 portrait un-identified man, undated; 78(IX):277 (Box-folder 17/76)
  - NBC Photo 1967 portrait un-identified man & woman, undated; 78(IX):278 (Box-folder 17/77)
  - NBC Photo 1967 portrait un-identified man, undated; 78(IX):279 (Box-folder 17/78)
  - NBC Photo 1967 portrait un-identified woman, undated; 78(IX):280 (Box-folder 17/79)
  - NBC Photo 1967 portrait un-identified man, undated; 78(IX):281 (Box-folder 17/80)
  - NBC Photo 1967 portrait un-identified woman, undated; 78(IX):282 (Box-folder 17/81)
  - NBC Photo 1967 portrait un-identified man & woman, undated; 78(IX):283 (Box-folder 17/82)
  - Huntley-Brinkley JFK Oval Office IV, undated; 78(IX):284 (Box-folder 17/83)
  - cleaning fish, undated; 78(IX):285 (Box-folder 17/84)
  - Big Sky in the lodge gift shop, undated; 78(IX):286 (Box-folder 17/85)
  - Big Sky big sky condos, undated; 78(IX):287 (Box-folder 17/86)
  - Big Sky big sky condos, undated; 78(IX):288 (Box-folder 17/87)
  - Big Sky ranch house log cabin home, undated; 78(IX):289 (Box-folder 17/88)
  - Big Sky 17 people looking at building plans, undated; 78(IX):290 (Box-folder 17/89)
  - Big Sky "Arnold Palmer 'Golf talk'", undated; 78(IX):291 (Box-folder 17/90)
  - Big Sky Arnold Palmer in design phase over diorama, undated; 78(IX):292 (Box-folder 17/91)
  - Big Sky group shot; US ski team hopefuls, undated; 78(IX):293 (Box-folder 17/92)
  - Big Sky deer, undated; 78(IX):294 (Box-folder 17/93)
  - Big Sky landscape shot of the mountain, undated; 78(IX):295 (Box-folder 17/94)
  - Big Sky landscape shot of the mountain, undated; 78(IX):296 (Box-folder 17/95)
  - Big Sky inspecting building plans, undated; 78(IX):297 (Box-folder 17/96)
  - Big Sky the building phase, undated; 78(IX):298 (Box-folder 17/97)
  - Big Sky looking over building plans, undated; 78(IX):299 (Box-folder 17/98)
  - Big Sky landscape shot of the mountain, undated; 78(IX):300 (Box-folder 17/99)
  - Big Sky color landscape shot of the mountain, undated; 78(IX):301 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Big Sky building going up, undated; 78(IX):302 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Big Sky the ranch, undated; 78(IX):303 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Big Sky building going up, undated; 78(IX):304 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Big Sky building going up, undated; 78(IX):305 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Big Sky church at Big Sky, undated; 78(IX):306 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Big Sky top of the chairlift, undated; 78(IX):307 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Big Sky the gondola, undated; 78(IX):308 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Big Sky 3 people on horseback, undated; 78(IX):309 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Big Sky getting on the chairlift, undated; 78(IX):310 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Big Sky Arnold Palmer/Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):311 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Big Sky fresh turns in powder, undated; 78(IX):312 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Big Sky landscape shot, undated; 78(IX):313 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - Big Sky landscape shot dirt road, undated; 78(IX):314 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Big Sky fresh turns in powder, undated; 78(IX):315 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Big Sky "Chet fly fishing the Yellowstone", undated; 78(IX):316 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Big Sky "welcome to Bozeman March 1970", 78(IX):317 (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Big Sky gondola, undated; 78(IX):318 (Box-folder 18/18)
  - Big Sky "Lone Peak triple chair", undated; 78(IX):319 (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Big Sky "Andesite double chair", undated; 78(IX):320 (Box-folder 18/20)
  - Big Sky "Après ski Activities Jimmers bar", undated; 78(IX):321 (Box-folder 18/21)
  - Big Sky "Lookout cafeteria", undated; 78(IX):322 (Box-folder 18/22)
  - Big Sky "Mountain Village hostel", undated; 78(IX):323 (Box-folder 18/23)
  - Big Sky "Cross Dam to Mountain Village - Deer Lodge Condominiums", undated; 78(IX):324 (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Big Sky "administration houses and employee housing", undated; 78(IX):325 (Box-folder 18/25)
  - Big Sky "The Huntley lodge", undated; 78(IX):326 (Box-folder 18/26)
  - Big Sky "Teepee trading Post", undated; 78(IX):327 (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Big Sky fly fisherman netting fish, undated; 78(IX):328 (Box-folder 18/28)
  - Big Sky golf tee shot, undated; 78(IX):329 (Box-folder 18/29)
  - Big Sky Big Sky lodging, undated; 78(IX):330 (Box-folder 18/30)
  - Big Sky Big Sky-summer lodging, undated; 78(IX):331 (Box-folder 18/31)
  - Big Sky Big Sky-art gathering, undated; 78(IX):332 (Box-folder 18/32)
  - Big Sky trap shooting, undated; 78(IX):333 (Box-folder 18/33)
  - Big Sky basketball game, undated; 78(IX):334 (Box-folder 18/34)
  - Big Sky enjoying the comforts of a lodge, undated; 78(IX):335 (Box-folder 18/35)
  - Big Sky corral, undated; 78(IX):336 (Box-folder 18/36)
  - Big Sky playing pool at the lodge, undated; 78(IX):337 (Box-folder 18/37)
  - Big Sky Big Sky golf, undated; 78(IX):338 (Box-folder 18/38)
  - Big Sky Big Sky tennis, undated; 78(IX):339 (Box-folder 18/39)
  - Big Sky Big Sky skiing, undated; 78(IX):340 (Box-folder 18/40)
  - Big Sky Big Sky luncheon, undated; 78(IX):341 (Box-folder 18/41)
  - Big Sky dinner buffet, undated; 78(IX):342 (Box-folder 18/42)
  - Big Sky skiing the mountaintop, undated; 78(IX):343 (Box-folder 18/43)
  - Big Sky riding the chairlift, undated; 78(IX):344 (Box-folder 18/44)
  - Big Sky fresh ski turns in powder, undated; 78(IX):345 (Box-folder 18/45)
  - Big Sky The Lodge at Big Sky Montana, undated; 78(IX):346 (Box-folder 18/46)
  - Big Sky approaching Big Sky, undated; 78(IX):347 (Box-folder 18/47)
  - Big Sky "Big Sky Information center VPM Reservations & Real Estate Offices", undated; 78(IX):348 (Box-folder 18/48)
  - Big Sky "start Silver Bow 1971", 78(IX):349 (Box-folder 18/49)
  - Big Sky "Meadow Village commercial", undated; 78(IX):350 (Box-folder 18/50)
  - Big Sky "winter in Meadow Village commercial", undated; 78(IX):351 (Box-folder 18/51)
  - Big Sky "summer in Meadow Village commercial", undated; 78(IX):352 (Box-folder 18/52)
  - Big Sky "Silver Bow I & II", undated; 78(IX):353 (Box-folder 18/53)
  - Big Sky "Black Otter Lodge", undated; 78(IX):354 (Box-folder 18/54)
  - Big Sky "Meadow Village Hostel", undated; 78(IX):355 (Box-folder 18/55)
  - Big Sky "Montana Power sub-station", undated; 78(IX):356 (Box-folder 18/56)
  - Big Sky "Meadow Village Homes and glacier", undated; 78(IX):357 (Box-folder 18/57)
  - Big Sky "Broadwater I", undated; 78(IX):358 (Box-folder 18/58)
  - Big Sky "Yellowstone and Golf Course", undated; 78(IX):359 (Box-folder 18/59)
  - Big Sky tennis courts, undated; 78(IX):360 (Box-folder 18/60)
  - Big Sky "Lone Mountain Guest Ranch Cabin", undated; 78(IX):361 (Box-folder 18/61)
  - Big Sky "Lone Mountain Guest ranch", undated; 78(IX):362 (Box-folder 18/62)
  - Big Sky Lone Mountain Ranch Sleigh Ride, undated; 78(IX):363 (Box-folder 18/63)
  - Big Sky "Camper village commercial", undated; 78(IX):364 (Box-folder 18/64)
  - Big Sky "Camper Village sites", undated; 78(IX):365 (Box-folder 18/65)
  - Big Sky "mobile home park", undated; 78(IX):366 (Box-folder 18/66)
  - Big Sky "medical clinic", undated; 78(IX):367 (Box-folder 18/67)
  - Big Sky "Ski the Sky Balloon", undated; 78(IX):368 (Box-folder 18/68)
  - Big Sky "cross country skiing", undated; 78(IX):369 (Box-folder 18/69)
  - Big Sky The 'Big Sky Montana' sign, undated; 78(IX):370 (Box-folder 18/70)
  - Big Sky "Meadow Village 1970", 78(IX):371 (Box-folder 18/71)
  - Big Sky "Crail ranch 1970", 78(IX):372 (Box-folder 18/72)
  - Big Sky Chet outdoor portrait leaning against the fence, undated; 78(IX):373 (Box-folder 18/73)
  - Big Sky inside the lodge, undated; 78(IX):374 (Box-folder 18/74)
  - Big Sky Lone Mountain ranch Sleigh ride; color, undated; 78(IX):375 (Box-folder 18/75)
  - Big Sky Lone Mountain landscape shot, undated; 78(IX):376 (Box-folder 18/76)
  - Big Sky Chet Huntley and Big Sky Montana sign, undated; 78(IX):377 (Box-folder 18/77)
  - Big Sky in the lodge gift shop, undated; 78(IX):378 (Box-folder 18/78)
  - Big Sky ranch, undated; 78(IX):379 (Box-folder 18/79)
  - Big Sky ranch, undated; 78(IX):380 (Box-folder 18/80)
  - Copy Negative: Huntley portrait signed, undated; 78(IX):381 (Box-folder 18/81)
  - Big Sky "water storage tank", undated; 78(IX):382 (Box-folder 18/82)
  - Big Sky Big Sky hot air ballooning, undated; 78(IX):383 (Box-folder 18/83)
  - Huntley, Nixon and Mrs Nixon, undated; 78(IX):384 (Box-folder 18/84)
  - Autographed photo, Chet Huntley and Nelson Rockefeller undated, 78(IX):431 (Box-folder 18/85)
  - Northern Pacific Wrecking Crain, undated; 78(IX):432 (Box-folder 18/86)
  - Big Sky planning session, undated; 78(IX):433 (Box-folder 18/87)
  - Huntley Brinkley at the news desk, undated; 78(IX):385 (Box-folder 24OS/1)
  - 69-12-16, cartoon photograph, undated; 78(IX):386 (Box-folder 24OS/2)
  - Huntley playing with a child, undated; 78(IX):387 (Box-folder 24OS/3)
  - Huntley playing with a child, undated; 78(IX):388 (Box-folder 24OS/4)
  - getting ready to go on camera, undated; 78(IX):389 (Box-folder 24OS/5)
  - boarding airplane, undated; 78(IX):390 (Box-folder 24OS/6)
  - Huntley Brinkley on the set, undated; 78(IX):391 (Box-folder 24OS/7)
  - at the typewriter, undated; 78(IX):392 (Box-folder 24OS/8)
  - on assignment, undated; 78(IX):393 (Box-folder 24OS/9)
  - on assignment, undated; 78(IX):394 (Box-folder 24OS/10)
  - on assignment, undated; 78(IX):395 (Box-folder 24OS/11)
  - portrait of Huntley at the news desk, undated; 78(IX):396 (Box-folder 24OS/12)
  - Huntley smoking pipe, undated; 78(IX):397 (Box-folder 24OS/13)
  - boarding airplane, undated; 78(IX):398 (Box-folder 24OS/14)
  - Huntley and Brinkley at the news desk, undated; 78(IX):399 (Box-folder 24OS/15)
  - Huntley at the news desk, undated; 78(IX):400 (Box-folder 24OS/16)
  - Huntley at the news desk (reversed), undated; 78(IX):401 (Box-folder 24OS/17)
  - "New York Herald Tribune photograph", undated; 78(IX):402 (Box-folder 24OS/18)
  - "New York Herald Tribune photograph", undated; 78(IX):403 (Box-folder 24OS/19)
  - on location, undated; 78(IX):404 (Box-folder 24OS/20)
  - office meeting, undated; 78(IX):405 (Box-folder 24OS/21)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):406 (Box-folder 24OS/22)
  - color portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):407 (Box-folder 24OS/23)
  - election night 1964, undated; 78(IX):408 (Box-folder 24OS/24)
  - Huntley playing with child, undated; 78(IX):409 (Box-folder 24OS/25)
  - portrait chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):410 (Box-folder 24OS/26)
  - sleeping at the airport, undated; 78(IX):411 (Box-folder 24OS/27)
  - election night 1964, undated; 78(IX):412 (Box-folder 24OS/28)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):413 (Box-folder 24OS/29)
  - Huntley Brinkley on the set election coverage 1966, 78(IX):414 (Box-folder 24OS/30)
  - election night 1964, undated; 78(IX):415 (Box-folder 24OS/31)
  - political cartoon photo I, undated; 78(IX):416 (Box-folder 24OS/32)
  - political cartoon photo II, undated; 78(IX):417 (Box-folder 24OS/33)
  - political cartoon photo III, undated; 78(IX):418 (Box-folder 24OS/34)
  - political cartoon photo IV, undated; 78(IX):419 (Box-folder 24OS/35)
  - political cartoon photo V, undated; 78(IX):420 (Box-folder 24OS/36)
  - portrait Chet Huntley, undated; 78(IX):421 (Box-folder 24OS/37)
  - Huntley Brinkley portrait drawn on city bench, undated; 78(IX):422 (Box-folder 24OS/38)
  - political cartoon photo VI, undated; 78(IX):423 (Box-folder 24OS/39)
  - political cartoon photo VII, undated; 78(IX):424 (Box-folder 24OS/40)
  - political cartoon photo VIII, undated; 78(IX):425 (Box-folder 24OS/41)
  - political cartoon photo IX, undated; 78(IX):426 (Box-folder 24OS/42)
  - political cartoon photo X, undated; 78(IX):427 (Box-folder 24OS/43)
  - Big Sky Panarama, undated; 78(IX):428 (Box-folder 24OS/44)
  - Chet Huntley posing at Big Sky Montana sign II, undated; 78(IX):429 (Box-folder 24OS/45)
  - Autographed photo, "Admiral C.W. Nimitz at the surrender of the Japanese, Tokyo Bay, September 2, 1945", 78(IX):430 (Box-folder 24OS/46)
- Audio and Moving Images, 1963-1974 and undated; Series X; 1.0 linear feet
  This series contains materials from several different media formats ranging from audiocassette tapes to 16 mm film reels. Contents include materials Huntley created during his broadcasting career, materials he collected for personal interest, as well as items of appreciation and memorial. Items 78(X):1 through 78(X):5 are LPs; 78(X):6 is an audio cassette of unknown relationship to Chet Huntley; 78(X):7 and 78(X):8 are reel-to-reel audio tapes; 78(X):9 through 78(X):16 are 16mm film; 78(X):17 is a Fairchild Moviepak Seventy 10 cassette (single-sided film within a cassette case), and 78(X):18 is a VHS cassette duplicating materials on film reels 78(X):10, 78(X):12, and 78(X):13. Items 78(X):19 through 78(X):24 are audio cassettes and reel-to-reel audio tapes that were added to this collection in 2017. Items 78(X):26 through 78(X):29 were donated as part of accession 2019-003.
  The series is divided into two subseries: Audio only, and Audio and Moving Images.
  - Subseries 1: Audio Only
    - "I'm in Love with Huntley and Brinkley," Serenade Records, undated; 78(X):1 (Box 21)
    - Interview with Mrs. P. A. Huntley (Blanche Huntley, Chet's mother), one year after "The Land", undated; 78(X):2 (Box 21)
    - "The Sound of the Crusade," The New York Conference of the Methodist Church, undated; 78(X):3 (Box 21)
    - "Huntley Piano," Mrs. Huntley, undated; 78(X):4 (Box 21)
    - Radio Moscow, undated; 78(X):5 (Box 21)
    - Mayor Daley, Chicago city council/interviews with Chicago residents, 1971-07-20; 78(X):6 (Box 21)
    - Chet Huntley on "Today" Show, 1970-07-31; 78(X):7 (Box 21)
    - Interview with Chet Huntley's mother (Blanche Huntley), 1963-05-12; 78(X):8 (Box 21)
    - Cassette tape copy of materials on audio reel 78(X):7, 1970-07-31; 78(X):19 (Box 21)
      A tape counter index accompanies the audio. The index was created by Archives and Special Collections.
    - NBC News Obituaries, circa 1974; 78(X):20 (Box 21)
      Individual newscasts by the following: John Chancellor, Edwin Newman, David Brinkley.
      A tape counter index, created by Archives and Special Collections, accompanies the audio.
    - Huntley news reports on Latin America and U.S./Great Britain progressivism, undated; 78(X):21 (Box 21)
    - Huntley news reports, 1974; 78(X):22 (Box 21)
    - Newsbreak obituary, 1974-03-21; 78(X):23 (Box 21)
      Charles Osgood reports on Chet Huntley's death
    - Chet Huntley World War II News Broadcasts, Tape 1, 1971-06-11; 78(X):24 (Box 21)
      Huntley's broadcasts about World War II that originally aired in 1943 and 1944. Compliations of these broadcasts were created by the Milo Ryan Phonoarchives, School of Communications, University of Washington.
    - Chet Huntley World War II News Broadcasts, Tape 1, 1971-06-11; 78(X):25 (Box 21)
    - Chet Huntley’s “Montana”, undated; 78(X):26; 45 RPM LP Record (Box 21)
    - Chet Huntley Presents Best of Washington Humor, 1963; 78(X):27; LP Record (Box 21)
    - Wall Street Speaks to Chet Huntley, 1963; 78(X):28; LP Record (Box 21)
    - Chet Huntley Talks About Pennzoil, circa 1969; 78(X):29; 45 RPM LP Record (Box 21)
  - Subseries 2: Audio and Moving Images
    - Big Sky, Construction of Ski Village and Ski Runs, November 1973; Shots of winter with snow on the ground. 2:00.; 16 mm; Color, 100 ft, No Sound (Reel 078(X):9)
    - NBC Nightly News Obit, 1974; John Chancellor, featuring David Brinkley. Includes Huntley's Network News Farewell.; 16 mm; Color, 350 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):10)
    - SOF Interview at Big Sky Resort, Interviewer Rita Shaw, November 11, 1973; 9:43; 16 mm; Color, 400 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):11)
    - Today, Obit, 1974; Featuring Frank Reynods, Walter Cronkite, and Edwin Newman.; 16 mm; Color, 541 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):12)
    - "What Happened to Chet Huntley", 1973; Huntley's last interview on Broadcast Journalism, Interviewer: Dick Hawkins.; 16 mm; Color, 929 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):13)
    - The American Experience, "Faiths of our Fathers" narrated by Huntley, Undated; Featuring Christopher Walken as H.D. Thoreau. 16:00; 16 mm; Color, 2,000 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):14)
    - The American Experience, "Strange and Terrible Times" narrated by Huntley, Undated; 16 mm; Color, 2,000 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):15)
    - "The Quiet War" narrated by Huntley, Undated; A report on cancer research at the University of Chicago, 26:00; 16 mm; Color, 1,000 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):16)
    - Chet Huntley on Big Sky Real Estate, 1972; Super 8 mm; Color, 200 ft, Sound (Reel 078(X):17)
    - Chet Huntley on Big Sky real estate, DVD duplicate, 1972; 78(X):17 (Box 21)
    - VHS copy of materials on film reels 78(X):10, 78(X):12, and 78(X):13, 1973-1974; 78(X):18 (Box 21)
- Awards, Memorials, and Memorabilia, 1954-1974; Series XI; 6.0 linear feet
  The materials in this series include mounted plaques, medallions, certificates of award and appreciation, honorary degrees, and memorial declarations bestowed upon Chet Huntley as a result of his professional career as well as one item of memorabilia. Three items in this series were bestowed with a parchment certificate. The one item of memorabilia in this series is a button inscribed with "Goodnight David, Goodnight Goliath," relating to Huntley's retirement from NBC News.
  - American Hungarian Studies Foundation, George Washington Award, 1970; 78(XI):13 (Box 19)
  - George Foster Peabody Radio Award, 1954; 78(XI):14 (Box 19)
  - University of Missouri, Medal for Distinguished Service in Journalism, undated; 78(XI):15 (Box 19)
  - Peace medal, unknown context, undated; 78(XI):16 (Box 19)
  - "Goodnight David, Goodnight Goliath" button, undated; 78(XI):17 (Box 19)
  - American Legion Auxiliary, Golden Mike Award, 1960; 78(XI):18 (Box 19)
  - Overseas Press Club of America, Best Radio or TV Interpretation of Foreign Affairs, 1958; 78(XI):19 (Box 25)